[
  [
    {
      "type": "mc",
      "question": "7 + 3 =",
      "choices": [
        "11",
        "9",
        "10",
        "12"
      ],
      "answer": "10"
    },
    {
      "type": "mc",
      "question": "7 + 3 =",
      "choices": [
        "11",
        "9",
        "10",
        "12"
      ],
      "answer": "10"
    },
    {
      "type": "mc",
      "question": "5 + 4 =",
      "choices": [
        "7",
        "9",
        "10",
        "11"
      ],
      "answer": "9"
    },
    {
      "type": "mc",
      "question": "4 + 3 =",
      "choices": [
        "7",
        "10",
        "9",
        "8"
      ],
      "answer": "7"
    },
    {
      "type": "mc",
      "question": "11 - 5 =",
      "choices": [
        "16",
        "15",
        "6",
        "4"
      ],
      "answer": "6"
    },
    {
      "type": "mc",
      "question": "17 + 5 =",
      "choices": [
        "20",
        "19",
        "21",
        "22"
      ],
      "answer": "22"
    },
    {
      "type": "mc",
      "question": "15 - 9 =",
      "choices": [
        "6",
        "24",
        "10",
        "9"
      ],
      "answer": "6"
    },
    {
      "type": "mc",
      "question": "16 + 17 =",
      "choices": [
        "22",
        "29",
        "33",
        "32"
      ],
      "answer": "33"
    },
    {
      "type": "sa",
      "question": "14 - 7 =",
      "answer": "7"
    },
    {
      "type": "sa",
      "question": "15 - 15 =",
      "answer": "0"
    },
    {
      "type": "sa",
      "question": "21 + 17 =",
      "answer": "38"
    }
  ],
  
  [
    {
      "type": "mc",
      "question": "15 + 13 =",
      "choices": [
        "28",
        "25",
        "29",
        "30"
      ],
      "answer": "28"
    },
    {
      "type": "mc",
      "question": "17 + 13 =",
      "choices": [
        "37",
        "35",
        "40",
        "30"
      ],
      "answer": "30"
    },
    {
      "type": "mc",
      "question": "30 + 5 + 14 =",
      "choices": [
        "50",
        "49",
        "39",
        "47"
      ],
      "answer": "49"
    },
    {
      "type": "mc",
      "question": "18 + 3 - 5 =",
      "choices": [
        "16",
        "19",
        "20",
        "26"
      ],
      "answer": "16"
    },
    {
      "type": "mc",
      "question": "59 - 27 =",
      "choices": [
        "39",
        "20",
        "30",
        "32"
      ],
      "answer": "32"
    },
    {
      "type": "mc",
      "question": "27 + 47 - 32 =",
      "choices": [
        "42",
        "52",
        "39",
        "59"
      ],
      "answer": "42"
    },
    {
      "type": "mc",
      "question": "87 - 13 - 26 =",
      "choices": [
        "48",
        "37",
        "50",
        "51"
      ],
      "answer": "48"
    },
    {
      "type": "sa",
      "question": "75 + 8 - 40 =",
      "answer": "43"
    },
    {
      "type": "sa",
      "question": "13 + 13 + 13 =",
      "answer": "39"
    },
    {
      "type": "sa",
      "question": "45 + 25 + 10 =",
      "answer": "80"
    }
  ],

  [
    {
      "type": "mc",
      "question": "Sarah has 3 apples, and Tom gives her 4 more. How many apples does Sarah have now?",
      "choices": [
        "6",
        "10",
        "7",
        "11"
      ],
      "answer": "7"
    },
    {
      "type": "mc",
      "question": "A farmer has 14 cows and buys 4 more. How many cows does he have now?",
      "choices": [
        "18",
        "15",
        "20",
        "14"
      ],
      "answer": "18"
    },
    {
      "type": "mc",
      "question": "Ben has 9 pencils, and her friend gives her 1 more. How many pencils does Lisa have now?",
      "choices": [
        "12",
        "11",
        "10",
        "15"
      ],
      "answer": "10"
    },
    {
      "type": "mc",
      "question": "Jenny has 8 stickers and finds 2 more on the floor. How many stickers does she have now?",
      "choices": [
        "10",
        "12",
        "9",
        "6"
      ],
      "answer": "10"
    },
    {
      "type": "mc",
      "question": "There are 4 birds sitting on a tree, and 3 more birds join them. How many birds are on the tree now?",
      "choices": [
        "7",
        "4",
        "11",
        "9"
      ],
      "answer": "7"
    },
    {
      "type": "mc",
      "question": "Tim has 10 candies, and his friend gives him 10 more. How many marbles does Tim have now?",
      "choices": [
        "10",
        "20",
        "15",
        "18"
      ],
      "answer": "20"
    },
    {
      "type": "mc",
      "question": "There are 17 fish in the pond, and 5 more fish are added. How many fish are in the pond now?",
      "choices": [
        "20",
        "14",
        "12",
        "22"
      ],
      "answer": "22"
    },
    {
      "type": "sa",
      "question": "There are 5 red balloons and 6 blue balloons at the party. How many balloons are there in total?",
      "answer": "11"
    },
    {
      "type": "sa",
      "question": "A basket contains 2 apples, 3 oranges, and 4 bananas. How many pieces of fruits are in the basket?",
      "answer": "9"
    },
    {
      "type": "sa",
      "question": "Class A has 15 students and class B has 14 students. How many students are there in total?",
      "answer": "29"
    }
  ],

  [
    {
      "type": "mc",
      "question": "Jamie has 8 candies, and he eats 5 of them. How many candies does Jamie have left?",
      "choices": [
        "7",
        "3",
        "4",
        "6"
      ],
      "answer": "3"
    },
    {
      "type": "mc",
      "question": "There are 10 birds on a tree, and 4 of them fly away. How many birds are left on the tree?",
      "choices": [
        "6",
        "8",
        "9",
        "3"
      ],
      "answer": "6"
    },
    {
      "type": "mc",
      "question": "Maria has 7 balloons, and 2 of the pop. How many balloons does Maria have now?",
      "choices": [
        "5",
        "3",
        "7",
        "6"
      ],
      "answer": "5"
    },
    {
      "type": "mc",
      "question": "A farmer has 9 sheep, and he sells 5 of them. How many sheep does the farmer have now?",
      "choices": [
        "7",
        "3",
        "5",
        "4"
      ],
      "answer": "4"
    },
    {
      "type": "mc",
      "question": "Jack has 17 pencils, and he gives 7 to her friend. How many pencils does Jack have left?",
      "choices": [
        "10",
        "9",
        "11",
        "12"
      ],
      "answer": "10"
    },
    {
      "type": "mc",
      "question": "There are 22 cookies in a jar, and Time eats 8 of them. How many cookies are left in the jar?",
      "choices": [
        "16",
        "18",
        "14",
        "12"
      ],
      "answer": "14"
    },
    {
      "type": "mc",
      "question": "Shelly has 36 toys, and she loses 16 of them. How many toys does Shelly have now?",
      "choices": [
        "10",
        "16",
        "26",
        "20"
      ],
      "answer": "20"
    },
    {
      "type": "sa",
      "question": "Sarah had 27 apples, but she gave 8 to her neighbour. How many apples does Sarah have left?",
      "answer": "19"
    },
    {
      "type": "sa",
      "question": "There are 18 books on a shelf, and 9 of them are taken away. How many books are left on the shelf?",
      "answer": "9"
    },
    {
      "type": "sa",
      "question": "Jemma has 14 stickers, and she gives 11 to her brother. How many stickers does Jemma have now?",
      "answer": "3"
    }
  ],

  [
    {
      "type": "mc",
      "question": "10 x 7 =",
      "choices": [
        "70",
        "17",
        "56",
        "48"
      ],
      "answer": "70"
    },
    {
      "type": "mc",
      "question": "7 x 9 =",
      "choices": [
        "48",
        "72",
        "63",
        "55"
      ],
      "answer": "63"
    },
    {
      "type": "mc",
      "question": "5 x 6 =",
      "choices": [
        "42",
        "30",
        "27",
        "48"
      ],
      "answer": "30"
    },
    {
      "type": "mc",
      "question": "8 x 4 =",
      "choices": [
        "67",
        "56",
        "24",
        "32"
      ],
      "answer": "32"
    },
    {
      "type": "mc",
      "question": "28 / 2 =",
      "choices": [
        "14",
        "15",
        "20",
        "17"
      ],
      "answer": "14"
    },
    {
      "type": "mc",
      "question": "18 x 3 =",
      "choices": [
        "54",
        "30",
        "60",
        "57"
      ],
      "answer": "54"
    },
    {
      "type": "mc",
      "question": "150 / 5 =",
      "choices": [
        "30",
        "60",
        "45",
        "55"
      ],
      "answer": "30"
    },
    {
      "type": "sa",
      "question": "26 x 5 =",
      "answer": "130"
    },
    {
      "type": "sa",
      "question": "85 / 5 =",
      "answer": "19"
    },
    {
      "type": "sa",
      "question": "15 x 16 =",
      "answer": "240"
    }
  ],

  [
    {
      "type": "mc",
      "question": "There are 3 baskets with 4 apples in each basket. How many apples are there in total?",
      "choices": [
        "15",
        "18",
        "10",
        "12"
      ],
      "answer": "12"
    },
    {
      "type": "mc",
      "question": "A spider has 8 legs. How many legs do 5 spiders have?",
      "choices": [
        "40",
        "45",
        "50",
        "30"
      ],
      "answer": "40"
    },
    {
      "type": "mc",
      "question": "Each packet contains 6 cookies. If there are 7 packets, how many cookies are there altogether?",
      "choices": [
        "42",
        "36",
        "48",
        "20"
      ],
      "answer": "42"
    },
    {
      "type": "mc",
      "question": "There are 10 shelves with 9 books on each shelf. How many books are there in total?",
      "choices": [
        "90",
        "82",
        "66",
        "95"
      ],
      "answer": "90"
    },
    {
      "type": "mc",
      "question": "Each flower has 5 petals. How many petals do 12 flowers have?",
      "choices": [
        "40",
        "50",
        "30",
        "60"
      ],
      "answer": "60"
    },
    {
      "type": "mc",
      "question": "A week has 7 days. How many days are there in 4 weeks?",
      "choices": [
        "21",
        "14",
        "30",
        "28"
      ],
      "answer": "28"
    },
    {
      "type": "mc",
      "question": "There are 8 rows of chairs with 5 chairs in each row. How many chairs are there in total?",
      "choices": [
        "40",
        "50",
        "60",
        "30"
      ],
      "answer": "40"
    },
    {
      "type": "sa",
      "question": "Each carton contains 8 eggs. If you have 13 cartons, how many eggs do you have?",
      "answer": "104"
    },
    {
      "type": "sa",
      "question": "A cow has 4 legs. How many legs does 23 cows have?",
      "answer": "92"
    },
    {
      "type": "sa",
      "question": "A car has 4 wheels, and a motorcycle has 2 wheels. How many wheels does 5 cars, and 8 motorcycles have?",
      "answer": "36"
    }
  ],

  [
    {
      "type": "mc",
      "question": "There are 12 apples, and you want to share them equally among 4 friends. How many apples will each friend get?",
      "choices": [
        "4",
        "2",
        "3",
        "5"
      ],
      "answer": "3"
    },
    {
      "type": "mc",
      "question": "A baker has 20 cookies and wants to put them into 5 boxes. How many cookies will go in each box?",
      "choices": [
        "6",
        "5",
        "4",
        "7"
      ],
      "answer": "4"
    },
    {
      "type": "mc",
      "question": "There are 15 balloons, and you want to divide them into groups of 3. How many students will be in each group?",
      "choices": [
        "5",
        "3",
        "4",
        "8"
      ],
      "answer": "5"
    },
    {
      "type": "mc",
      "question": "A teacher has 30 students and wants to form 6 equal groups. How many students will be in each group?",
      "choices": [
        "5",
        "7",
        "8",
        "4"
      ],
      "answer": "5"
    },
    {
      "type": "mc",
      "question": "You have 18 marbles and want to split them equally into 3 bags. How many marbles will each bag contain?",
      "choices": [
        "9",
        "5",
        "6",
        "4"
      ],
      "answer": "9"
    },
    {
      "type": "mc",
      "question": "There are 40 pieces of candy, and you want to divide them equally among 5 friends. How many pieces of candy?",
      "choices": [
        "4",
        "6",
        "8",
        "7"
      ],
      "answer": "8"
    },
    {
      "type": "mc",
      "question": "A farmer has 28 apples and wants to pack them into boxes, with each box containing 7 apples. How many boxes will he need?",
      "choices": [
        "4",
        "6",
        "5",
        "2"
      ],
      "answer": "4"
    },
    {
      "type": "sa",
      "question": "Timmy has 16 toy cars and want to divide them into 4 equal groups. How many cars will be in each group?",
      "answer": "4"
    },
    {
      "type": "sa",
      "question": "A gardener has 27 flowers and wants to plant them in 9 equal rows. How many flowers will be in each row?",
      "answer": "3"
    },
    {
      "type": "sa",
      "question": "There are 36 crayons, and you want to distribute them equally among 6 kids. How many crayons will each kid get?",
      "answer": "6"
    }
  ],

  [
    {
      "type": "mc",
      "question": "There are 48 pencils, and you want to put them into 4 equal groups. How many pencils will be in each group?",
      "choices": [
        "15",
        "16",
        "12",
        "14"
      ],
      "answer": "12"
    },
    {
      "type": "mc",
      "question": "A farmer has 54 oranges and wants to divide them equally among 9 baskets. How many oranges will go in each basket?",
      "choices": [
        "5",
        "8",
        "6",
        "7"
      ],
      "answer": "6"
    },
    {
      "type": "mc",
      "question": "There are 40 students in a class, and the teacher wants to form teams of 4. How many teams will there be?",
      "choices": [
        "10",
        "8",
        "11",
        "6"
      ],
      "answer": "10"
    },
    {
      "type": "mc",
      "question": "You have 72 candies and want to distribute them equally among 8 friends. How many candies will each friend get?",
      "choices": [
        "11",
        "9",
        "8",
        "10"
      ],
      "answer": "9"
    },
    {
      "type": "mc",
      "question": "A library has 64 books and wants to arrange them on 8 shelves. How many books will be on each shelf?",
      "choices": [
        "6",
        "7",
        "8",
        "9"
      ],
      "answer": "8"
    },
    {
      "type": "mc",
      "question": "There are 27 cupcakes, and you want to put them into boxes with 3 cupcakes in each box. How many boxes will you need?",
      "choices": [
        "5",
        "8",
        "7",
        "9"
      ],
      "answer": "9"
    },
    {
      "type": "mc",
      "question": "A gardener has 81 flowers and wants to plant them in 9 equal rows. How many flowers will be in each row?",
      "choices": [
        "9",
        "5",
        "8",
        "7"
      ],
      "answer": "9"
    },
    {
      "type": "sa",
      "question": "Jackie has 45 pencils and want to divide them equally into 5 boxes. How many pencils will be in each box?",
      "answer": "9"
    },
    {
      "type": "sa",
      "question": "There are 56 bottles, and you want to distribute them equally among 7 trashcans. How many bottles will be in each trashcan?",
      "answer": "8"
    },
    {
      "type": "sa",
      "question": "A baker bakes 60 cookies and wants to equally give them to 12 kids. How many cookies will each kid get?",
      "answer": "5"
    }
  ]
]